YSAAC ANDUJAR

• Software Engineer •

ABOUT ME

I am a software engineer specialized in creating efficient solutions for large companies. I am passionate about learning and mastering new technologies, always aiming to provide value with dedication. My focus is on working responsibly, driving projects in an agile manner, and achieving effective results.

EDUCATION

Software Engineering

Universidad del Caribe

Software Development

Instituto Tecnológico de Las Américas

Electronics Technician

Instituto Politécnico Pilar Constanzo

PORTFOLIO

Website: https://yandujar.netlify.app/

GitHub: https://github.com/YsaacAndujar

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ysaac-andujar-binet-982517232/

EXPERIENCE

Codika - Software Engineer

2023 - Present

• Create different projects for large companies such as: Centro Cuesta Nacional, Banco Popular Dominicano, Bondelic, SkyHigh, Metaldom, Analisa, Seprisa, among others.

Kalifika - Software Engineer

2023 - Present

• Develop a BackOffice and Backend for Kalifka, as well as assist in creating the business logic for the application.

Tennos Business - Software Engineer

2022 - 2023

- Maintain and create new modules to the "MagyNet" CRM.
- Maintain and create new modules for the "MagyPago" platform.

SRC - FullStack Developer

2022 - 2022

- In charge of creating a BackOffice for a mobile application about telephone recharges and purchasing lottery tickets.
- In charge of creating the API's to connect the BackOffice with the mobile app.

SKILLS

LANGUAGES

Languages

Typescript, C#, Python.

Spanish - Native **English**- Advanced

Frameworks:

React, NodeJs, .Net, Django, Angular, Vue

DataBases

SqlServer, MySql, MongoDb, PostgreSQL